<?xml version="1.0"?>
<Container version="2">
  <Name>BubbleUPnP</Name>
  <Repository>fireplex/bubbleupnp</Repository>
  <Registry/>
  <Network>host</Network>
  <Privileged>false</Privileged>
  <Support/>
  <Overview>BubbleUPnP Server</Overview>
  <Category/>
  <WebUI>http://[IP]:[PORT:58050]</WebUI>
  <TemplateURL/>
  <Icon>https://lh6.ggpht.com/L5IDTYtc4hFL-X97zxQ6Uuy2n2kB_ZxZ76SCZGAKVWd4hwYFEvl-rMWgvpcLAlBwOhBB=w300-rw</Icon>
  <Description>
    BubbleUPnP Server provides new services, many of them running on top of your existing UPnP/DLNA devices:
make various media formats not natively supported by Chromecast playable with transcoding. Works in tandem with Android BubbleUPnP
secure Internet access to your UPnP/DLNA Media Servers content with Android BubbleUPnP and foobar2000.
stream and download your music, video, photos with your Android device from a mobile or WiFi connection with optional transcoding to reduce bandwidth.
no need to sync, to upload to the cloud, to register to an online service
create OpenHome Media Renderers from any UPnP AV or Google Cast renderer (provides on-device playlist, multiple Control Point access to the same renderer)
create an UPnP/DLNA renderer from any Google Cast device
fix issues of UPnP/DLNA Media Servers (discovery issues, broken data, add some audio DLNA compliance) by creating a proxy Media Server
access your UPnP/DLNA Media Servers across different networks
BUBBLEUPNP SERVER IS NOT AN UPNP AV MEDIA SERVER.
Unless BubbleUPnP Server is used only for use with Chromecast, it requires at least one working UPnP AV Media Server or Media Renderer to do something useful.
  </Description>
    <Networking>
    <Mode>host</Mode>
    <Publish>
      <Port>
        <HostPort>58050</HostPort>
        <ContainerPort>58050</ContainerPort>
        <Protocol>tcp</Protocol>
      </Port>
    </Publish>
  </Networking>
    <Data>
    <Volume>
      <HostDir>/mnt/user/appdata/bubbleupnp/</HostDir>
      <ContainerDir>/config</ContainerDir>
      <Mode>rw</Mode>
    </Volume>
  </Data>
  <Environment/>
  <Config Name="HTTP" Target="58050" Default="" Mode="tcp" Description="Container Port: " Type="Port" Display="always" Required="false" Mask="false">58050</Config>
  <Config Name="Config" Target="/config" Default="" Mode="rw" Description="Container Path: /config" Type="Path" Display="always" Required="false" Mask="false">/mnt/user/appdata/bubbleupnp/</Config>

 </Container>
